<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Huawei &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<atom:link href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/category/mobile-phone/huawei/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<description>Know what you think</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:53:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/cropped-download-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Huawei &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Huawei P30 Pro</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Huawei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=18</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[We certainly understand why many of the UK&#8217;s biggest retailers have gone a bit quiet about their Huawei P30 Pro deals in recent months. Making&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-19" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80.jpg 650w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80-300x168.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" /></figure>



<p>We certainly understand why many of the UK&#8217;s biggest retailers have gone a bit quiet about their Huawei P30 Pro deals in recent months. Making headlines after Google had to cut ties with the company, there is no doubt that the Huawei brand is somewhat stigmatised right now. </p>



<p>But in an odd turn of events, that now makes the best camera phone on the market a suddenly affordable option. A host of deals from Mobiles.co.uk mean you can now get a Huawei P30 Pro at a discount of up to £120. </p>



<p>While there is a risk of Huawei losing its access to Android updates and other important features of the phone, there are also other possible outcomes. With Trump&#8217;s next move almost impossible to predict and a number of American companies rallying against the ban and a proposed trade deal that could drop it all together, Huawei could go back to normal before we even know it.</p>



<p>Or, if the ban stays in place, Huawei has proposed its own operating system that it plans to launch instead of Android. Either way, you&#8217;ll have the world&#8217;s second best smartphone at a majorly reduced price.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ve listed all of the best Huawei P30 Pro deals from this Mobiles.co.uk price drop below. With prices as low as this, depending on how you see it, there has never been a better (or, possibly, worse) time to get this device.</p>



<p>listed all of the best Huawei P30 Pro deals from this Mobiles.co.uk price drop below. With prices as low as this, depending on how you see it, there has never been a better (or, possibly, worse) time to get this device.</p>



<h2 id="how-good-is-the-huawei-p30-pro">How good is the Huawei P30 Pro?</h2>



<p>Before the ban took place, the Huawei P30 Pro was receiving praise as one of the most innovative devices out there, with a lot of that praise aimed at its camera. Sporting an incredible 50x zoom camera, smart AI camera features and an overall impeccable quality, nothing can quite match it.</p>



<p>Backing up the camera is a high quality inifinity display screen, tonnes of power and a massive battery. In other words the Huawei P30 Pro is here battling for the spot of the world&#8217;s best phone &#8211; just with more than a few reservations.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
