<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Xiaomi Mobiles &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<atom:link href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/category/mobile-phone/xiaomi-mobiles/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<description>Know what you think</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/cropped-download-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Xiaomi Mobiles &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MI 9T, XIAOMI’S</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Mobiles]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=21</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Qualcomm®Snapdragon™730 with an increasing CPU and GPU performance Mi 9T features the best-in-class Qualcomm®&#160;Snapdragon™&#160;730 mobile platform, offering an increase of 35 percent for CPU performance,&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-300x300.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-22" width="372" height="372" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-300x300.jpg 300w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-150x150.jpg 150w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-768x768.jpg 768w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-230x230.jpg 230w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 372px) 100vw, 372px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Qualcomm®</strong><strong>Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong><strong>730 with an increasing CPU and GPU performance</strong></p>



<p>Mi 9T features the best-in-class Qualcomm®&nbsp;Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />&nbsp;730 mobile platform, offering an increase of 35 percent for CPU performance, and of 10 percent for GPU, as well as twice the AI performance, compared to its predecessor Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />&nbsp;710– all enabled an octa-core KryoTM&nbsp;470 chip processor based on the 8nm process for extreme power efficiency, along with the 4th generation AI smart engine for delivering powerful AI performance.</p>



<p>The smartphone comes with the new Game Turbo 2.0 for an ultimate gaming experience by optimizing touch response, display, sound quality, network and in-game calls. Touch response rate goes up to 180Hz, while click and touch response times are reduced to about 70 milliseconds, the new Mi 9 family member is able to offer an esports-level gaming experience.</p>



<p><strong>AMOLED Full Screen Display and unique curved glass back with flame design</strong></p>



<p>Featuring a 6.39-inch AMOLED screen without a notch, the display of Mi 9T supports Reading and Sunlight mode 2.0, low-brightness color grayscale optimization, and 256-scale eye protection technology, delivering an incredible immersive viewing experience. It has also received low-blue-light eye protection certification by Germany’s VDE Testing and Certification Institute. By adopting an elegant pop-up selfie solution, Mi 9T is able to achieve a true full screen display.</p>



<p>Mi 9T applies a nano-holographic technology to produce a unique flame design on its four-sided curved glass back. The combination of 3D-glass and extremely narrow frame gives the phone an incredibly comfortable hand-feel.</p>



<p>The device is equipped with the 7th-generation in-screen fingerprint technology. The dual optimization of hardware and software significantly improves the fingerprint recognition rate and speed.</p>



<p><strong>48MP triple camera and 20MP pop-up front camera</strong></p>



<p>Offering an AI triple camera setup, Mi 9T features a main 48MP camera with a 1/2″ Sony flagship IMX 582 sensor that can produce ultra-high resolution photos. For night portraits, the camera sensor supports merging four pixels to form large 1.6μm pixels to capture more details in low-light conditions.</p>



<p>In addition to the 48MP main camera, the Mi 9T also features a 13MP ultra wide-angle lens with a 124.8 degree field of view, and an 8MP telephoto lens. The options offered by the combination of these three lenses can cover most settings, delivering an SLR-like photography experience.</p>



<p>Mi 9T sports a 20MP pop-up front-facing camera with a sapphire glass cover. When the front camera is raised, it will display lighting effects and is accompanied by one of six sound effects. The light ring on top acts as a notification light for incoming messages and charging status. Group selfies taken with the panorama feature, which allows panning the 20MP selfie camera, will let you include all your friends in a single shot.</p>



<p><strong>4000mAh large battery, NFC and Hi-Res Audio certification</strong></p>



<p>Featuring a large 4000mAh battery and an AI energy saving mode to automatically adjust screen brightness and for activating sleep mode at night, Mi 9T has power to last through a day of heavy use. Mi 9T supports up to 18W charging.</p>



<p>Mi 9T offers multi-function NFC, with payment transaction speeds increased by up to 30 percent. It also offers superb audio quality, featuring 1217SLS speakers and Smart PA as well as a 0.9cc large sound chamber for powerful playback. The device retains a 3.5mm headphone jack, and has received Hi-Res Audio certification.</p>



<p><strong>Price and availability</strong></p>



<p>Mi 9T will be available in Spain from 17 June with two colors, Carbon Black and Glacier Blue, at a retail price of €329 for 6GB + 64GB. For the first 24 hours, mi.com/es and Amazon will feature a special launch price of €299 for the 6GB + 64GB version. The 6GB + 128GB model, available in Spain in the coming weeks, will be priced at €369. The Flame Red version will come at a later date.</p>



<p>Availability in other markets will be announced closer to local launch dates.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
