<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<atom:link href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<description>Know what you think</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/cropped-download-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>admin &#8211; Blog Here</title>
	<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Elon Musk believes electric planes will become more practical in about 5 years</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/elon-musk-believes-electric-planes-will-become-more-practical-in-about-5-years/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/elon-musk-believes-electric-planes-will-become-more-practical-in-about-5-years/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=28</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[For as easy as it is to poke fun at Elon Musk’s online shenanigans, there’s no denying that he was able to revolutionize the auto&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/elon-musk-believes-electric-planes-will-become-more-practical-in-about-5-years/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/electric-plane.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-29" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/electric-plane.jpg 782w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/electric-plane-300x201.jpg 300w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/electric-plane-768x516.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 782px) 100vw, 782px" /></figure>



<p>For as easy as it is to poke fun at Elon Musk’s online shenanigans, there’s no denying that he was able to revolutionize the auto industry in a relatively short period of time. Thanks to the initial success of the Model S, Tesla was able to prove that electric cars didn’t have to be clunky eyesores. What’s more, the popularity of the Model S — along with the Model Y and the Model 3 — definitively proved that demand for EVs was far greater than anyone could have anticipated even a few years ago.</p>



<p>Tesla’s obsession with all things electric, of course, extends far beyond traditional four-door sedans, an assertion bolstered by Tesla’s acquisition of SolarCity and the company’s plans to roll out an electric-powered semi-truck and pickup truck in the near future.</p>



<p>Beyond that, is it perhaps possible that Tesla will one day leverage its EV expertise to develop an airplane? It certainly sounds far-fetched, but as evidenced by Musk’s work with The Boring Company, it’s practically impossible to anticipate what Musk will get into next. That said, someone asked Musk via Twitter a few days ago about whether or not an electric powered plane would be feasible.</p>



<p>“Yes,” Musk responded, “but still a bit too limited on range. That will change in coming years as battery energy density improves.”</p>



<p>“Jet A (kerosene) has much higher energy density than Li-ion, but electric motors weigh much less &amp; convert stored energy to motion better than combustion engines,” Musk later added. Lastly, Musk noted that he anticipates lithium-ion batteries will be able to compete with kerosene in about five years time.</p>



<p>Of course, Musk’s comments on Twitter prompted many to wonder if Tesla might someday get into aviation. Personally, I don’t think so, but stranger things have happened once Musk becomes fixated on an idea.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/elon-musk-believes-electric-planes-will-become-more-practical-in-about-5-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>LG is about to unveil an Android phone</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/lg-is-about-to-unveil-an-android-phone/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/lg-is-about-to-unveil-an-android-phone/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[LG Mobiles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=24</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[The LG G8 ThinQ that we saw in a variety of leaks before MWC isn’t exactly a secret. As has been the case in previous&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/lg-is-about-to-unveil-an-android-phone/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-v50-mwc-2019-event-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-26" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-v50-mwc-2019-event-1.jpg 782w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-v50-mwc-2019-event-1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-v50-mwc-2019-event-1-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 782px) 100vw, 782px" /></figure>



<p>The LG G8 ThinQ that we saw in a variety of leaks before MWC isn’t exactly a secret. As has been the case in previous years, LG has already unveiled some of the features of the phones and teased others.</p>



<p>LG revealed a few weeks ago that the G8 ThinQ will feature support for 3D face recognition just like the iPhone X, XR, and XS phones. That means the handset will have a noticeable notch just like the iPhones. On top of that, the same front-facing 3D cameras and sensors should let users control their phones with gestures. That’s something LG also teased ahead of the show, without fully detailing the feature.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-crystal-sound-oled.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-25" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-crystal-sound-oled.jpg 782w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-crystal-sound-oled-300x162.jpg 300w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/lg-g8-thinq-crystal-sound-oled-768x413.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 782px) 100vw, 782px" /></figure>



<p>A few days later, LG shared with the world one more exciting ThinQ feature, the Crystal Sound OLED (CSO) tech that turns the entire screen into a speaker.</p>



<p>There aren’t too many phones that support 3D face recognition, let alone gesture-based navigation. And there’s no widely available handset in the world with a display that also doubles as a speaker. If that’s not enough, LG’s V50 ThinQ is also supposed to make a showing during the press conference. That’s LG’s first 5G phone according to reports, a device that should be release in stores later this year.</p>



<p>We’ll get you all the details on both phones from LG’s keynote, make sure you follow along below beginning at 1:30 PM EST.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/lg-is-about-to-unveil-an-android-phone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MI 9T, XIAOMI’S</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Mobiles]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=21</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Qualcomm®Snapdragon™730 with an increasing CPU and GPU performance Mi 9T features the best-in-class Qualcomm®&#160;Snapdragon™&#160;730 mobile platform, offering an increase of 35 percent for CPU performance,&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-300x300.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-22" width="372" height="372" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-300x300.jpg 300w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-150x150.jpg 150w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-768x768.jpg 768w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024-230x230.jpg 230w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Mi-9T_01-1024x1024.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 372px) 100vw, 372px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Qualcomm®</strong><strong>Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong><strong>730 with an increasing CPU and GPU performance</strong></p>



<p>Mi 9T features the best-in-class Qualcomm®&nbsp;Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />&nbsp;730 mobile platform, offering an increase of 35 percent for CPU performance, and of 10 percent for GPU, as well as twice the AI performance, compared to its predecessor Snapdragon<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />&nbsp;710– all enabled an octa-core KryoTM&nbsp;470 chip processor based on the 8nm process for extreme power efficiency, along with the 4th generation AI smart engine for delivering powerful AI performance.</p>



<p>The smartphone comes with the new Game Turbo 2.0 for an ultimate gaming experience by optimizing touch response, display, sound quality, network and in-game calls. Touch response rate goes up to 180Hz, while click and touch response times are reduced to about 70 milliseconds, the new Mi 9 family member is able to offer an esports-level gaming experience.</p>



<p><strong>AMOLED Full Screen Display and unique curved glass back with flame design</strong></p>



<p>Featuring a 6.39-inch AMOLED screen without a notch, the display of Mi 9T supports Reading and Sunlight mode 2.0, low-brightness color grayscale optimization, and 256-scale eye protection technology, delivering an incredible immersive viewing experience. It has also received low-blue-light eye protection certification by Germany’s VDE Testing and Certification Institute. By adopting an elegant pop-up selfie solution, Mi 9T is able to achieve a true full screen display.</p>



<p>Mi 9T applies a nano-holographic technology to produce a unique flame design on its four-sided curved glass back. The combination of 3D-glass and extremely narrow frame gives the phone an incredibly comfortable hand-feel.</p>



<p>The device is equipped with the 7th-generation in-screen fingerprint technology. The dual optimization of hardware and software significantly improves the fingerprint recognition rate and speed.</p>



<p><strong>48MP triple camera and 20MP pop-up front camera</strong></p>



<p>Offering an AI triple camera setup, Mi 9T features a main 48MP camera with a 1/2″ Sony flagship IMX 582 sensor that can produce ultra-high resolution photos. For night portraits, the camera sensor supports merging four pixels to form large 1.6μm pixels to capture more details in low-light conditions.</p>



<p>In addition to the 48MP main camera, the Mi 9T also features a 13MP ultra wide-angle lens with a 124.8 degree field of view, and an 8MP telephoto lens. The options offered by the combination of these three lenses can cover most settings, delivering an SLR-like photography experience.</p>



<p>Mi 9T sports a 20MP pop-up front-facing camera with a sapphire glass cover. When the front camera is raised, it will display lighting effects and is accompanied by one of six sound effects. The light ring on top acts as a notification light for incoming messages and charging status. Group selfies taken with the panorama feature, which allows panning the 20MP selfie camera, will let you include all your friends in a single shot.</p>



<p><strong>4000mAh large battery, NFC and Hi-Res Audio certification</strong></p>



<p>Featuring a large 4000mAh battery and an AI energy saving mode to automatically adjust screen brightness and for activating sleep mode at night, Mi 9T has power to last through a day of heavy use. Mi 9T supports up to 18W charging.</p>



<p>Mi 9T offers multi-function NFC, with payment transaction speeds increased by up to 30 percent. It also offers superb audio quality, featuring 1217SLS speakers and Smart PA as well as a 0.9cc large sound chamber for powerful playback. The device retains a 3.5mm headphone jack, and has received Hi-Res Audio certification.</p>



<p><strong>Price and availability</strong></p>



<p>Mi 9T will be available in Spain from 17 June with two colors, Carbon Black and Glacier Blue, at a retail price of €329 for 6GB + 64GB. For the first 24 hours, mi.com/es and Amazon will feature a special launch price of €299 for the 6GB + 64GB version. The 6GB + 128GB model, available in Spain in the coming weeks, will be priced at €369. The Flame Red version will come at a later date.</p>



<p>Availability in other markets will be announced closer to local launch dates.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/mi-9t-xiaomis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huawei P30 Pro</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Huawei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=18</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[We certainly understand why many of the UK&#8217;s biggest retailers have gone a bit quiet about their Huawei P30 Pro deals in recent months. Making&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-19" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80.jpg 650w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/qHMbS7hmoo6TzhbffHnu9d-650-80-300x168.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" /></figure>



<p>We certainly understand why many of the UK&#8217;s biggest retailers have gone a bit quiet about their Huawei P30 Pro deals in recent months. Making headlines after Google had to cut ties with the company, there is no doubt that the Huawei brand is somewhat stigmatised right now. </p>



<p>But in an odd turn of events, that now makes the best camera phone on the market a suddenly affordable option. A host of deals from Mobiles.co.uk mean you can now get a Huawei P30 Pro at a discount of up to £120. </p>



<p>While there is a risk of Huawei losing its access to Android updates and other important features of the phone, there are also other possible outcomes. With Trump&#8217;s next move almost impossible to predict and a number of American companies rallying against the ban and a proposed trade deal that could drop it all together, Huawei could go back to normal before we even know it.</p>



<p>Or, if the ban stays in place, Huawei has proposed its own operating system that it plans to launch instead of Android. Either way, you&#8217;ll have the world&#8217;s second best smartphone at a majorly reduced price.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ve listed all of the best Huawei P30 Pro deals from this Mobiles.co.uk price drop below. With prices as low as this, depending on how you see it, there has never been a better (or, possibly, worse) time to get this device.</p>



<p>listed all of the best Huawei P30 Pro deals from this Mobiles.co.uk price drop below. With prices as low as this, depending on how you see it, there has never been a better (or, possibly, worse) time to get this device.</p>



<h2 id="how-good-is-the-huawei-p30-pro">How good is the Huawei P30 Pro?</h2>



<p>Before the ban took place, the Huawei P30 Pro was receiving praise as one of the most innovative devices out there, with a lot of that praise aimed at its camera. Sporting an incredible 50x zoom camera, smart AI camera features and an overall impeccable quality, nothing can quite match it.</p>



<p>Backing up the camera is a high quality inifinity display screen, tonnes of power and a massive battery. In other words the Huawei P30 Pro is here battling for the spot of the world&#8217;s best phone &#8211; just with more than a few reservations.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/huawei-p30-pro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Galaxy S10</title>
		<link>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/samsung-galaxy-s10/</link>
				<comments>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/samsung-galaxy-s10/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Samsung Mobiles]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/?p=7</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Almost the best phone in the world, overshadowed by its big brother Release date:&#160;March 2019 &#124;&#160;Weight:&#160;157g &#124;&#160;Dimensions:&#160;149.9 x 70.4 x 7.8mm &#124;&#160;OS:&#160;Android 9 &#124;&#160;Screen size:&#160;6.1-inch&#8230; <span><a href="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/samsung-galaxy-s10/">( Read More )</a></span>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80.jpg 650w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80-300x168.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" /></figure>



<p>Almost the best phone in the world, overshadowed by its big brother</p>



<p><strong>Release date:&nbsp;</strong>March 2019 |&nbsp;<strong>Weight:&nbsp;</strong>157g |&nbsp;<strong>Dimensions:&nbsp;</strong>149.9 x 70.4 x 7.8mm |&nbsp;<strong>OS:&nbsp;</strong>Android 9 |&nbsp;<strong>Screen size:&nbsp;</strong>6.1-inch |&nbsp;<strong>Resolution:&nbsp;</strong>1440 x 3040 |&nbsp;<strong>CPU:&nbsp;</strong>Snapdragon 855 / Exynos 9820 |&nbsp;<strong>RAM:&nbsp;</strong>8GB |&nbsp;<strong>Storage:&nbsp;</strong>128/512GB |&nbsp;<strong>Battery:&nbsp;</strong>3,400mAh |&nbsp;<strong>Rear camera:&nbsp;</strong>12MP + 12MP + 16MP |&nbsp;<strong>Front camera:&nbsp;</strong>10MP</p>



<p>It&#8217;s close at the top, with Huawei snapping at Samsung&#8217;s heels it&#8217;s never been tougher for the South Korean firm, and the S10 is getting elbowed.</p>



<p>The bigger S10 Plus is by far Samsung&#8217;s best phone, but the standard S10 backs almost all the same top-end features into a more compact form factor and slightly lower price tag (but still steep).RECOMMENDED VIDEOS FOR YOU&#8230; </p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80-1-150x150.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-9" srcset="https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/PgFh9SRUAwKdhsG8p8dZu6-650-80-1-230x230.jpg 230w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></figure></div>



<p style="text-align:left"></p>



<p>

 With a 6.1-inch display you&#8217;re not exactly getting a small screen with the standard S10, but Samsung has reduced bezels even more over the S9, keeping the dimensions surprisingly compact.&nbsp;You also get a fingerprint scanner embedded in the display. 

</p>



<p><strong>Battery life:</strong> The battery in the S10 has grown versus the one in the S9, but with the increased screen size as well you&#8217;re still looking at all-day battery life with a nightly charge. The S10 also has Samsung&#8217;s new Wireless PowerShare, allowing you to wirelessly charge other devices on the rear of the handset.</p>



<p><strong>Camera:</strong>&nbsp;Like the S10 Plus, the trio of cameras on the Galaxy S10 are among the best on the market, building on the excellent setup on the S9 series by offering more features, shooting modes and overall clarity.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Mini verdict:</strong>&nbsp;The Samsung Galaxy S10 gets proper under-the-hood upgrades. You’ll like all of these powerful features, while your friends will like the new Wireless PowerShare perk – it helps them out more than you.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://abdulrafayzahid.github.io/blogHere/2019/07/02/samsung-galaxy-s10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
